

Samarinda, East Kalimantan

INTRODUCTION -

Experienced Back - End Developer with over 3 years of practical experience. Proficient in utilizing Go and PHP programming languages to build efficient websites with a focus on creating efficient websites that work smoothly. Committed to producing clean, maintainable code and optimizing backend processes to improving efficiency for delivering reliable solutions that align with user and business requirements. I'm eager to contribute my technical expertise to collaborative projects and learning to become better

E	+62 813-5135-9343
\triangle	harris.for.work@gmail.com
\mathbb{X}	/harrisishaq_
0	/harrisishaq
in	/harris-ishaq-ibrahim

EXPERIENCE -

Aug 2021 - Dec 2023

Back-End Developer | Diacon Medica Technologies

Working as a Back-End Developer, primarily utilizing the Golang programming language with Echo Framework. Key responsibilities include:

- Developing and implementing new features for the company's product, "Carevo" Apps.
- Participating in project-based programs, such as healthcare and banking sectors.
- Collaborating with mobile and front-end developers to create REST API services.
- Integrating third-party APIs into our products and projects for enhanced functionality.

Sep 2020 - Jul 2021

Back-End Developer | AJAR.id

- As a Back-End Developer, contributed to the development of new features for our product, AJAR Learning Management System (LMS), using PHP programming language and Laravel framework.
- Actively monitored the system and conducted bug fixes, contributing to the continuous improvement of usability and overall system quality.

Jan 2020 - Aug 2021

Freelance Web Developer | ID Core Indonesia

Contributed to several projects as a Web Developer, using PHP programming language with the Laravel Framework. The projects encompassed areas such as Payroll and Employee Management, News Portal, and Maintenance/Repair Service Products.

To delve deeper into my work experience and explore additional details of my work history, feel free to check out my LinkedIn profile.

■EDUCATION -

Formal Education

†

2015 - 2020

University of Muhammadiyah Malang, MalangDepartments of Informatics.

2012 - 2015

Vocational High School 7, SamarindaDepartments of Software Engineering.

Non - Formal Education (Workshop / Certification)



2019

Digital Talent Scholarship | Ministry of Communications & Informatics

Participated in a workshop on Python Programming for Machine Learning purposes.



Java Fundamental Certifications | Oracle Academy Participated in a workshop on Java Fundamental.

SKILL-

Programming

- Web Development: Golang with Echo Framework, PHP with Laravel and Codelgniter Framework.
- Other Programming Language: Python for Machine Learning purposes, Java & Javascript.
- Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, ArangoDB, and Redis.
- Other: AWS, Postman, Github, Gitlab, Bitbucket, Termius, and Portainer.

Language

- Indonesia: Native Language
- English: Passive in speaking but good understanding in reading and listening.
- Korean: Capable of reading and writing only, but can understand a few words.